Privacy Policy
==============

The Vegas Strip Commitment
--------------------------

Vegas Strip, and its staff, value your privacy and the privacy of all the information you give us. We aim to be completely transparent in our processes and protocols, so your information is never used without your consent. Please read our Privacy Policy below and contact us immediately if you have any questions.

The Information We Collect
--------------------------

Vegas Strip collects two different forms of personal information – log file analysis information (‘Traffic Information’) and visitor registration information (‘User Information’) – including personal information such as name, phone number, and email address. By visiting and signing up with https://www.vegasstripcasino.com/ you are agreeing to your disclosure of this information.

### Traffic Information

Vegas Strip routinely gathers Information on Site activity, such as data on how many people visit the Site, the pages they visit, where they come from, how long they stay, etc.

This information is collected on an anonymous basis, which means no personal information is associated with this data (unless first entry is via an affiliate).

Vegas Strip uses cookies and web server logs to track repeat visitors to its site, however these cookies do not collect specific information until the user registers with Vegas Strip. This information is used to better design our site, improve navigation and help us create targeted marketing with affiliates.

Vegas Strip collects certain technical information from your computer each time you request a page during a visit. This information is collected from your computer's Web browser to enhance your experience on our site and may include your IP address, operating system, Web browser software (e.g. Chrome, Firefox, Safari or Internet Explorer), screen resolution, and referrer Website.

### User Information

Vegas Strip may ask you to provide User Information, to register for an account or participate in contests or promotions. The information requested may include your name, address, e-mail address, shipping information, phone number, credit card or other payment information. User Information is collected only when Site visitors voluntarily provide it. It is not necessary to provide any User Information to simply browse the Site.

Your Information may be shared with our employees, independent contractors, agents or other related entities and/or business partners acting on our behalf to fulfill an award or promotion; conduct surveys; collect payments or to provide a product or service you have requested. We do not share this information with non-partner companies except to the extent necessary to complete your transaction (such as with Neteller, your bank, your credit card company) and, when we do share it, it is subject to their agreement to treat it as confidential business information and with the understanding that it may not be used for any purpose other than to perform their function.

https://www.vegasstripcasino.com/ may have inbound links from other websites, including affiliate partners. These sites have their own Privacy policies, which do not apply to Vegas Strip.

We release Information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with law, to enforce or apply our Terms and Conditions and other agreements, or to protect the rights, property, or safety of users or others. This includes exchanging Information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

Vegas Strip Marketing
---------------------

As a registered user, you may receive emails or phone calls from us about special promotions, surveys, contests, sweepstakes, newsletters about Vegas Strip and its marketing partners. We may also use your e-mail address or telephone number to contact you about changes to your account.  
  
To assess the effectiveness of these emails, we may attach a trackable URL (on an image within the email) that provides confirmation when you open an email. This only occurs if your computer supports such technology. To protect your right not to provide us with this information, modern email clients, such as Outlook, only send this tracking information to us when you have enabled such a feature, as it is disabled by default, in your mail client tool options.  
  
In order to supply accurate advertising features (such as language specific banners), our advertising system logs IP addresses.

Vegas Strip values your time and membership and will thus aim to follow all marketing protocols with due respect to you the user. If the user requests to not be contacted via a certain method, we will make all due efforts in order to abide by the user’s wishes.

Data Security
-------------

All transactions and Player activities within the member’s area of Vegas Strip are fully encrypted with 256 bit SSL Security certificate. This means that Vegas Strip deploys similar security to that of most financial institutions and guarantees the safety and privacy of all its members and their information.  
  
However, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be completely secure, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us, and you transmit such information at your own risk.  
  
Our Network security team is constantly seeking out the newest and best security programs and protocols. Security of information is of paramount importance to Vegas Strip.

Will Vegas Strip Casino sell my information to any third parties?
-----------------------------------------------------------------

Vegas Strip Casino does not sell any of its player’s personal information to third parties. 

Vegas Strip Casino may provide aggregate statistics about our players, internet traffic, sales, and related site information to a reputable third party. However, these statistics will not include any personally identifying information.

Vegas Strip Casino also allows its players to opt out of any mails that they do not wish to receive from us. Just send an email to [help@vegasstripcasino.com](mailto:help@vegasstripcasino.com). You may also unsubscribe by clicking the unsubscribe link in our emails.

Vegas Strip Casino is committed to respecting and protecting your privacy.

Changes in the Privacy Policy
-----------------------------

Vegas Strip reserves the right to change its Privacy Policy at any time. All changes will be effective immediately upon posting. We advise members to frequently visit this page to be aware of any such changes.

Copyright 2024 - All Rights Reserved. We invite you to review the [Terms & Conditions](https://www.thevirtualcasino.com/terms.php) - [Privacy Policy](https://www.thevirtualcasino.com/privacy.php)

Standard Terms & Conditions apply to all available promotions, unless specifically stated otherwise.
